Nguyen Vinh Thien

Fresher Developer

Phone: 0394 756 393

Email: vinhthien1996@gmail.com

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/vinhthien1996

Github: https://github.com/vinhthien1996

ABOUT ME

I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, responsible and hard working person. Besides, I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using own initiative.

My goal is to be a professional developer in the next 2 years at young and dynamic environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TopDev

10/2020 - Present

Position: Intern Developer (Laravel) Responsibilities:

Research available source code.

 Develop some more simple functions from the existing project.

04/2019 - 05/2020

Nguyen Gia Media

Posotion: Designer Responsibilities:

 Website administration, banner design, standee, advertising video editing for brand advertising.

EDUCATION

09/2020 - Present

CyberSoft Academy

Front-end (ReactJS, Angular), Fulstack (NodeJS, VueJS)

07/2020 - 10/2020

Korea IT School

Java web (Spring MVC)

08/2015 - 08/2018

Vinh Long University of Technology Education

Software Application

GPA: 3.59/4

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, ReactJS, Redux, NodeJS, Java, PHP (Laravel), MySQL, MongoDB, GIT

- English (Basic Reading Comprehension)

PROJECT

In my free time, I work on some projects:

- Git: https://github.com/vinhthien1996
- Weather App

http://vinhthien-weather-app.herokuapp.com/

- Clone Tix Homepage

http://vinhthien-tix.surge.sh/

- Clone Udemy Old Homepage

http://vinhthien-udemy.surge.sh/

- Movie Star Homepage

http://vinhthien-bootstrap.surge.sh/